{
    "id": "e445243e1a9c4108bd95332ea78340c6",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We will have to do something ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quick",
                "quickly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7178275ab09445178414b5b853b7d3ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "She danced……………………………. into the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "happily"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7c289fdb5d64eb2939ffa74964d5a9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fish was …………………………. cooked.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59c844f5807647e1844952439c5f4700"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t remember him very ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94fd52e241a147a782d699f2bea7f995"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………………… hot today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terrible",
                "terribly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8df972f54ad4ab9855f629994d01ce8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was driving …………………………… fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unusual",
                "unusually"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c45734fec67241afb3106d3ba6688d10"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………….. in love with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mad",
                "madly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d0d04e4fcab4d7f867d452331890722"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate arriving ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ba4f6aba1c64b65ac0df43c66e4e429"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ……………………….. punished for his crimes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "justly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "80eadf396c274a5eb20ae384b91db274"
        },
        {
            "question": "My husband ………………………… forgot my birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "complete",
                "completely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "86b828c49d944b72ba905e0bebfb6d6b"
        }
    ]
}